out of the interior of the business.
So the place and the interior is a key factor.
It is not just the organization that will be better at the forefront,
but also people who perform the foresight should also win
something on this by getting a chance to apply
their skills in a new world, a new area.
Since we are Vinnova and the Innovation Authority in Sweden
so is it important to us that this stay is relevant
for innovation and we usually say that if one understands
the future a little better or the possible future a little better so
Do you get better at leading from the future and that is why we
is worth better should be able to formulate a strategy for those when
This applies to various future issues and this may apply to technology.
The
may apply to community development or other types of risks
As he imagines may come in the future.
We wish the person who makes the residence to have been allowed to apply
their skills and learned something by having received
Access to 1 new location and a new business.
And we hope this will be medially or communicative
in the sense that others can be inspired and take part in
The result.
Something short about formalia then
Anyone seeking it should be the municipality, region or authority.
You seek as a lone organization.
In the application, one should then also describe this person who
performed the residence.
The person who then has skills in foresight.
It is a person you have the task of finding, identifying
and describe and that person is also part of the assessment late
Then the assessment process itself.
When we look at the applications.
There are different ways to
engage that person if one hires a person on something
And as I have been in, it is important to this at
some way and long term it is about the ability of the organization
To be innovative in forward forward simply.
The point of the residence is that you meet.
And different.
Skills that the organization has a type of knowledge and
skill and this person performing the residence has one
Other knowledge so that something new is added.
So if
that to speak is distance between the person and
The organization's competence will arise as an extra
Interesting meeting.
For us at my mom so it is interesting if our support is playing
Is there any interesting aspect of knowledge transfer
When you end up on the inside of an organization of an organization
and becomes part of it.
It is interesting in the application to try to understand how
The organization is renewed by welcoming this person
with new skills.
And as I have also been on so or interesting out of portfolio
Perspective If more organizations can open the eyes
For this with individual mobility and residence.
So that the communicative how to spread and how to tell
What you learn is also interesting to.